Guide to the Jim Fouratt Papers
Fouratt (Jim) Papers
- Band demos and recordings, 1980 1989; Series IV; 77.42 Linear Feet; (78 boxes); 1347 Audiocassettes; 7 Audiotape Reels
  - Ancestors, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 108, Item barcode 39002140906992)
  - Apprehended, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 108, Item barcode 39002140906984)
  - Eric Jay, Erotics, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 108, Item barcode 39002140906976)
  - Ear Scenery, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:08:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 108, Item barcode 39002140906968)
  - Brodoff, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:39:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio is unbalanced at times. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906091)
  - Appliances, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the program can be heard. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906109)
  - Eyes, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906117)
  - The Exciters, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the program are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow and unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906125)
  - Blue Angel, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906133)
  - Coup D'Etat, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906141)
  - Cosmic Overdose, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:18:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Crosstalk is present. Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906158)
  - Coolies, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906166)
  - The Rousers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. Static is present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906174)
  - Rufty Tufty, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906182)
  - The Crackers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906190)
  - Circus Mort, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002137159472)
  - Bound + Gagged, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A warble can be heard in the audio for the first three seconds. Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906208)
  - Beast, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:31:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906216)
  - Bahama Mama, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906224)
  - The Dimentians, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906232)
  - The Erotics, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:50:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 109, Item barcode 39002140906240)
  - Dizzy + The Romilars, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - The Del-Byzanteens, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - The dB's, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Live at Deaf Club, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Ennui, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Disturbed Furniture, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - The Dance, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Delta 5, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - David Kelly, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - 'Dirty Looks' A.K.A. 'Dirty Crooks', Brain Educators, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Dan Zam, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Downtown Executives, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum can be heard. (Box 110, Item barcode 39002140950537)
  - Devine Monochord, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio hiss and hum are present. (Box 110, Item barcode 39002141022039)
  - The Dark, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Dale Williams Band, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - The Endgame Band, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Dune, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - Daddy Licks, 1980 1989 (Box 110)
  - R's, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904609)
  - The Stick Men, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904617)
  - Sharks, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904625)
  - Arson, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. High amounts of hum and static are present. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904633)
  - The Speedies, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:38:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904641)
  - The Pencils, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904658)
  - Pete Florance, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904666)
  - Casper, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:26:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program is in silence from 00:17:18-00:18:14. There is interference during the program. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904674)
  - The Pseudos, 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. Dropouts are present in the program. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904682)
  - Polyrock, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904690)
  - The Pseudos, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904708)
  - Sick Dick, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:45:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum can be heard. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140901449)
  - Neighbors and Allies, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static and dropouts are present on the tape. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904716)
  - The Nuclear Accidents, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:32:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904724)
  - Oleg, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. Audio distortion can be heard. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904732)
  - The Side Effects, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904740)
  - Sky, Carl Cohen, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 111, Item barcode 39002140904757)
  - Marilyn Roberts, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028606)
  - Numbers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028614)
  - Ralph Landis and Neon Wildlife, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028622)
  - The Mirrors, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028630)
  - Minors Aloud, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028663)
  - Street Dancer, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028655)
  - Poison Squirrel, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028648)
  - Phyllis MacBryde, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028705)
  - New Models, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028697)
  - 1994, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028689)
  - New York Space Ensemble, 1980; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028671)
  - Blue Movies, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028721)
  - The Blasters, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028713)
  - Bound + Gagged, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum and hiss are present. (Box 112, Item barcode 39002140908386)
  - 911, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028762)
  - Blowgun, 1979; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028754)
  - The Basics, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028747)
  - The Brains, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 112, Item barcode 39002141028739)
  - Certain Generals, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Certain Generals, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - China Shop, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Cherry + The Pickups, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Richard Craven Group, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Chemicals Made From Dirt, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Chemicals Made From Dirt, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - The Shades Crash Course In Science, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Coffe, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - The Crackers, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Chinas Comidas, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - B-52's, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Joey Balin & the Mirrors, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - The Charades, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - China Shop, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - Band Planet, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - The National Irrationals, 1980 1989 (Box 113)
  - The Most, 1980; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022294)
  - The Normals, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022302)
  - Numbers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022310)
  - "MONTST★Z", 1980; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022328)
  - Micky Clean, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022336)
  - Spit, 1980; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022344)
  - Rubber Rodeo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022351)
  - Troupe DiCoupe, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022369)
  - Not Heaven, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022377)
  - Pop Decay, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022385)
  - The Cheese, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022393)
  - Extreme Unction, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:26:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static and dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002140904468)
  - Borbetomagus (EMPTY), 1980 1989 (Box 114)
  - Everest the Hard Way, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022401)
  - China Shop, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022419)
  - The Coup, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022427)
  - Crash Course in Science, 1979; 1 Audiocassette (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022435)
  - The Eyes, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 114, Item barcode 39002141022443)
  - Brave Combo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028085)
  - Dune [case only], 1980 1989; The case is empty. No audiocassette is present. (Box 115)
  - Babylon Dance Band, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028077)
  - Baby Buddha, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027046)
  - Bowie, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028069)
  - The Basics, Go-Boys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028051)
  - The Bachelors, Even, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028044)
  - Big Stick, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028036)
  - Buckingham, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028028)
  - Bahama Mama, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028010)
  - Blue Riddim Band, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141028002)
  - Bob, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027996)
  - Ballistic Kisses, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027988)
  - Props, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027970)
  - No Exit, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027962)
  - None of the Above, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027954)
  - The Dance, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027939)
  - Domestic Exile - Young and Ambitious, 1980; 1 Audiocassette (Box 115, Item barcode 39002141027947)
  - Chemicals Made from Dirt, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159514)
  - The Decoys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159654)
  - The Boneheads, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:04:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159647)
  - The Erotics, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:29:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159639)
  - Dizzy + The Romilars, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:03:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159621)
  - Band of Outsiders, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:04:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159613)
  - The Change, 1978 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159605)
  - The Dogboys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. An echo in the audio can be heard at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159597)
  - "conceputol", 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159589)
  - Circus Mort, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159480)
  - "Casual T-Ease", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159571)
  - Contortions, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:30:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio dropouts are present. The sound is muffled. Audio hiss, hum, and distortion are also present. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159563)
  - Frank Berry, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159555)
  - Wade Barker, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159548)
  - Disturbed Furniture, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times. sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159530)
  - Double Cross, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159522)
  - The Dale Williams Band, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 116, Item barcode 39002137159662)
  - Dresden Danse, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141025057)
  - Vytrs Voice, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is in silence from 00:07:05-00:07:50. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141025040)
  - The Roys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141025032)
  - Big Game, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141025024)
  - The Dance, 1979 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141025016)
  - Bloomingdales, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. An echo in the program can be heard. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141025008)
  - The Corvairs, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:27 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024993)
  - Dinettes, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024985)
  - Chic, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program was recorded in the left channel only for the last 10 minutes of the tape. There is a warble in the audio. The last 10 minutes of the program is mono. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024977)
  - Click, 1979 April; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024969)
  - Ebenezer + The Bludgeons, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024951)
  - The Essentials, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024944)
  - Joe King Carrasco + The Crowns, 1980 March; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024936)
  - Cellmates, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024928)
  - Berlin, 1978; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024910)
  - The Beat, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024902)
  - The Beeks, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 0014:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141024894)
  - Boto Teen, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:23:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio hiss and hum are present. (Box 117, Item barcode 39002141022120)
  - Secrets, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159936)
  - Dreams Die Hard, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159944)
  - Dresden Danse, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. There is a warble in the audio. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159928)
  - Red Interiors, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159902)
  - The Sharks, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:01:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is muffled. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159852)
  - Pluto Pluck and the I Witness, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Speed fluctuations are present. The program is muffled. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159845)
  - Ravyns, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159878)
  - Uptown Atomics, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159860)
  - The Strain, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. The program is muffled. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159894)
  - Nurses, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159886)
  - The Nelson F. Ferrer Band, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program was recorded at a very high level at times. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159910)
  - Remod, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is distorted at times. Static is present. High amounts of buzz are present. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159837)
  - Quinn Richard, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002137159795)